// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The greatest distance of a planet from the sun is called what? Is it the planet's :",
    answer: "Aphelion",
    options: [
      "Aphelion",
      "Perihelion",
      "Helix",
      "Eccentricity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How is the atmospheric pressure of Mars as compared to the atmospheric pressure of the earth ?",
    answer: "about 1/200th that of the earth's",
    options: [
      "about the same as the earth's",
      "about 100 times as great as the earth's",
      "about 1/200th that of the earth's",
      "half as much as that of the earth's"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The planet Jupiter has a mass that is : ",
    answer: "greater than the combined masses of all of the planets",
    options: [
      "equal to the combined masses of the earth and Mars",
      "equal to the combined masses of Saturn and Pluto",
      "equal to the combined masses of Saturn, Neptune and Uranus",
      "greater than the combined masses of all of the planets"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "About how many light years across is the Milky Way .",
    answer: "1,00,000",
    options: [
      "1,000",
      "10,000",
      "1,00,000",
      "10,00,000"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Heliocentric (pron: he-lee-o-sen-trik) means around:",
    answer: "the Sun",
    options: [
      "Jupiter",
      "the Moon",
      "the Sun",
      "Neptune"
    ]
  },
  
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Who was the first man to classify stars according to their brightness.",
     answer: "Hipparchus",
    options: [
       "Aristarchus",
       "Pythagorus",
       "Copernicus",
       "Hipparchus"
     ]
   },
   
   {
      numb: 7,
     question: "For what reason was the Schmidt telescope specially built?",
     answer: "a sky camera",
    options: [
       "a sky camera",
       "a radio telescope",
       "an optical telescope",
       "a solar telescope"
     ]
   },
   { numb: 8,
     question: "Which one of the following moon features is named Copernicus ?",
     answer: "crater",
    options: [
       "sea",
       "crater",
       "mountain range",
       "rill"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 9,
     question: "A typical galaxy, such as our Milky Way galaxy, contains how many billion stars ?",
     answer: "200 billion",
    options: [
       "10 billion",
       "40 billion",
       "200 billion",
       "800 billion"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 10,
     question: "Which of the following is true for ORION ?",
     answer: "a constellation",
    options: [
       "the brightest star in the sky",
       "a constellation",
       "the name given to a NASA spacecraft",
       "an asteroid"
     ]
   },
];